{
  "letters": [
    {"key": "a"},
    {"key": "b"},
    {"key": "c"},
    {"key": "d"},
    {"key": "e"},
    {"key": "f"},
    {"key": "g"},
    {"key": "h"},
    {"key": "i"},
    {"key": "j"},
    {"key": "k"},
    {"key": "l"},
    {"key": "m"},
    {"key": "n"},
    {"key": "o"},
    {"key": "p"},
    {"key": "q"},
    {"key": "r"},
    {"key": "s"},
    {"key": "t"},
    {"key": "u"},
    {"key": "v"},
    {"key": "w"},
    {"key": "x"},
    {"key": "y"},
    {"key": "z"},
    {"key": " "}
  ],
  "solutions": [
    {"id": 1, "question": "What's brown and sticky?", "answer": "a stick"},
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What do you call a fake noodle?",
      "answer": "an impasta"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "How does the moon cut his hair?",
      "answer": "eclipse it"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What do you call a factory that makes okay products?",
      "answer": "a satisfactory"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What do you call a fish wearing a bowtie?",
      "answer": "sofishticated"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What kind of car does an egg drive?",
      "answer": "a yolkswagen"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "How many tickles does it take to make an octopus laugh?",
      "answer": "ten tickles"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What does a bee use to brush its hair?",
      "answer": "a honeycomb"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What do cats eat for breakfast?",
      "answer": "mice krispies"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What color is the wind?",
      "answer": "blew"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Who do you call to clean the ocean?",
      "answer": "mermaids"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Where do rainbows go after being arrested?",
      "answer": "prism"
    }
  ]
}
